{
    "subject": "King_Vidor",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Three_Wise_Fools__1923_film_",
    "human_readable": "King Vidor directed the film Three Wise Fools (1923).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9195509552955627,
            "question": "Is there a film directed by King Vidor released in 1923?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8596808910369873,
            "question": "In what year did King Vidor direct Three Wise Fools?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8287403583526611,
            "question": "Who directed the film Three Wise Fools?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6942698359489441,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by King Vidor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6899905204772949,
            "question": "Name a film directed by King Vidor."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6892555952072144,
            "question": "Does King Vidor have any other notable films besides Three Wise Fools?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6694076061248779,
            "question": "What year was the film Three Wise Fools released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5838294625282288,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring King Vidor as director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5002338886260986,
            "question": "What genre might the film Three Wise Fools belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3818681538105011,
            "question": "King Vidor was involved in which type of media?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=King Vidor directed the film Three Wise Fools (1923).",
            "html": "yago_21667_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the film Three Wise Fools belong to?",
            "html": "yago_21667_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film starring King Vidor as director?",
            "html": "yago_21667_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Three Wise Fools released?",
            "html": "yago_21667_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21667_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that King Vidor indeed directed the film \"Three Wise Fools\" (1923), as mentioned in several files, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21667/re-ranker-msmarco/69.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21667/re-ranker-msmarco/88.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"King Vidor directed the film Three Wise Fools (1923).\" Specifically, document 65.txt clearly states, \"Three Wise Fools (German title: Ein M\u00e4dchen und drei alte Narren) is a 1923 American silent drama film directed by King Vidor.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}